I received a package. A really big and sturdy package. And inside are three masks or rather
one mask with three fronts, a helmet. Really futuristic. I've got to show this. Stay tuned.
What's inside the box? This is inside the box and another visor. So this is kind of a helmet mask
with different fronts you can interchange them I saw this once at a
party and I was like wow this is so cool I need to know more about it and now I
am really happy that I can show you these kind of helmets also the inside
how it works and how it looks the manufacturer is Manja Jons I hope I
pronounced it correctly and this is the GT series so one back shell and three
front shells all interchangeable and working with the back shell and I'm
going to show you how to interchange the faces. You have to slightly press the
sides of the face part together and now it opens. You can see that there is a
snapping hook that connects the front part to the back side and you can open
it further and these are velcro stripes that attach the front to the back. You
can open them and detach them. They're really stretchy by the way. And now we got the front
separated from the back part. Now if I want to change them, so I'm going to take the
Velcro strips and attach them in the crown of the face part.
I'm putting them in there so the parts are connected.
And now that I attached the back part to the front part, by the way this is the front part
from the inside with the face, if you're interested in that, and you can close it again with pressing
this side slightly inwards and snapping them together.
With the mask there comes a super fluffy high quality microfiber cloth with which you can
clean the helmet again especially if you're wearing latex and hats and you
have all the fingerprints on the helmet it's super fast and easy to clean it
again with this it looks almost black it's a multi-layer coating so a lot of
work went into the coating and it's almost like a one-way mirror because you
can't really see inside but if you're wearing it you can definitely see
through it. I got rid of my high ponytail because I'm going to try on the first
variation, the one with the face part. It's called TC Diety and I'm just
putting the back part and the back of my hat like a hand and now trying to close
it
It's a bit more tricky to close it while wearing it but I think it's also simply practice.
And now I mean I can see through the visor.
I'm going to get rid of all the fingerprints.
pretty funny. It's a bit foggy, so fogging up because of my breath but there are
anti-fog agents which you could spray on the inside. So I can basically see
everything. It's a bit green tinted but I have no problem looking through the
visor and seeing everything.
So before I'm going to wear the next one I have to customize the inlay because
you can actually detach all the foam and there are
pieces of foam inside which I'm going to get rid of because it was a bit too tight.
So I'm removing the padding. Every mask comes with a bit of spare padding so you
can interchange it and as I said customize it. And now I'm going to put
that inside again. I think it's this way and it'll stick to the velcro in the
mask. Now I have a bit more space here. This is completely black but we have this kind of nose contouring here so it's not a smooth front but a bit of facial features and I have a really big field of vision because it's
completely see-through so I see actually more than with the mask before. I can
hear a bit worse with this one and it's really tight so I'm wearing size small.
There are different sizes available and yeah without the extra padding it fits
good but it is a snug fit which I think it's supposed to be. So since there are no
breathing holes in the mask itself the air is coming through here so it's
nothing for people with claustrophobia I'd say or having a hard time breathing
because the airflow is a bit limited but taking it off is actually quite fast and
easy so as you can see the design is quite thought through everything works
pretty well together. There is a lot of work in the design and also the
manufacturing process. It is not just a cheap costume, I'd rather say it's more like
a stage outfit. So think of Daft Punk for example and as I said I've seen her the
first time from worn by a performer at a party. So that was really really cool to
see and yeah I'm really happy that I can show them here. I think it's a really
cool product. I kind of feel like a robot with this helmet. So yeah I think it's
better to call this a helmet. There are no facial features left and I put on
some gloves too to give like the full sleek black visual here. So my nose is
touching the inside of the helmet. It's a tight fit. It's not too uncomfortable.
so it does work but you do notice that there is no nose shape here but like a shield
all right which one was your favorite of the three I'm quite curious I think
I like this one and also the face one because they're so different and her face is quite cute
but this is so futuristic I think this is my favorite and yeah would I wear this for a party
I don't know it's not my thing but they're quite comfortable so I can imagine that people will
wear them longer yeah thanks again to Manja Juntz for sending these along I really enjoyed this video
I love showing you guys new things and I hope you have some
Takeaway from this video and even if it is how it looks from the inside and how it works
Even if it's not your cup of tea
Leave a thumbs up anyway and a comment and subscribe to my channels and yes, thank you for watching
I will see you in the next video. Bye